Zachary Robin

Winter Park FL 32792 | zrobin88@gmail.com (407) 416-9895 https://zrobin88.github.io/updatedPortfolio/index.html www.linkedin.com/in/zachary-robin-02756789

SUMMARY

Entry-level web developer with a background in music-production and entertainment business. Proficient in front end and back end development with experience developing full-stack applications. Front end knowledge includes HTML/CSS/Javascript along with various front-end libraries such as React. Back end/database knowledge includes Node.js, Express, SQL, Sequelize, Mongo db and Mongoose.

SKILLS

Web Development Technologies

- HTML/CSS/ Javascript
- Github
- Node.js
- Express
- React.js
- mySQL/Mongo DB

Business and Management

- Project and Team Management
- Business Finance
- Business Plan Development
- Digital Marketing and SEO
- Effective in communication and team leadership

Music Production and Audio Engineering

- Proficient in Digital Audio Workstation software such as Pro Tools and Logic-X
- Concise understanding of signal flow and signal routing
- Proficient in microphone theory
- Proficient in Audio mixing and mastering

EXPERIENCE

(ZDR LLC) - Orlando FL

February 2012 - Present

Freelance Business Owner

- Audio recording/mixing/editing
- Web application development focused towards the music industry

Sirius I.Q. - Sarasota FL

February 2018 - July 2018

Web/Mobile Developer internship

- Front end development
 - Languages: Javascript, Typescript, Aurelia
 - Assisted with coding the User Interface and testing various functions of the app
 - Shadowed and assisted the developers with debugging

- Experience shadowing back-end and A.I. development
 - Observed back-end coding in C# and Node.js

The Imagination House Studio - Orlando FL

February 2017- July 2017

Internship

- Assisted the engineer with general studio duties such as: set up, strike down, pro tools session set up, operation of Avid S6 controller and more
- Running errands for the studio such as: food runs, taking checks to the bank, supply runs
- Troubleshooting equipment

GRP Studios - Longwood FL

June 2016 - November 2016

Internship

- Recorded, edited and mixed audio and video for television and music
- Session set up/strike in both hardware and software
 - Includes: Mics, Cue system, Pro Tools, Gain staging, Patchbay
- Troubleshooting any problems that would arise during the session
- Experience in spot checking audio and video in Pro Tools

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida - Orlando, FL Full-Stack-Developer Certificate

May 2019

Full Sail University - Winter Park FL

Master of Science in Entertainment Business Bachelor of Science in Recording Arts September 2018

August 2017

PROJECTS

Web Application Projects

- Managed a team of student developers in order to successfully create a full stack application from scratch
- Utilized Github to simulate working on projects in a real-world coding environment

Project and Team Management

 Involved in managing the budget, communication, planning, timing and logistics of various projects

Digital Marketing

Devised digital marketing and SEO plans for local businesses near Full Sail

Negotiation and Deal Making

Negotiating contracts, business deals and the underlying principles involved

Business Plan Development

- Developed a fully-functional business plan for my company
- Presented the business plan to a mock-panel of investors